Tarun Bhalla

Software Developer

Current honor student at York university pursuing a degree in Information Technology with a specialization in Object Oriented Programming. I have experience in programming and web design and a desire to learn and improve. Experience using front-end languages such as HTML, CSS and JavaScript, along with back-end programs such as Java, Python3 and C++.

Work History

2020-05 -2021-01

CS Hub (Computing Students Hub)

York University, Toronto, Ontario

- Vice president of CS Hub community.
- Gathered and recruited new members while also working on creative and engaging projects.
- Helped members with coding projects and assignments.

2018-10 -2020-01

Customer Experience Coordinator

TD Canada , Mississauga, ON

- -Helping customers do day-to-day transactions and dealing with customer disputes.
- -Successfully met and exceeded performance and referral goals every quarter at the position
- Counseled clients on financial matters and provided recommendations on investment opportunities, products and services based on client needs and asset availability.
- -Demonstrated self-reliance by meeting and exceeding workflow needs.

2015-03 -2018-10

Customer Experience Associate

TD Canada Trust, Mississauga, ON

- -Was tasked with helping customers do day to day transactions and for meeting sales and service goals.
- Successfully met all sales goals for each quarter
- -Finished in the top quartile for sales and service for 4 quarters
- Was tasked with training new employees
- Reviewed account and service histories to identify trends

Contact

Address

Brampton, Ontario, L6R 1L5

Phone

647-779-6178

E-mail

Tarunbhalla96@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/tarun-bhalla/

www

Skills

Logistics support

HTML

C++

Java

R Studio

Matlab Programming

Object Oriented Programming

GitHub

Python3

CSS

JavaScript

Linux

Superior time management

Software Development

and issues.

-Supported customer service goals and enhanced relations through friendly, knowledgeable and positive communication.

2015-01 - Salesman

ADT Alarms (Safety and Security), Brampton, ON

- -Was tasked cold calling and generating leads for service technician.
- Answered incoming telephone calls to provide information about products, services, store hours, policies and promotions.

Education

2015-05

2017-04 Bachelor of Arts: Social Sciences

York University - Toronto, ON

2018-09 - Bachelor of Arts: Information Technology

2021-07 York University - Toronto, ON